[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tomatoes can be refrigerated and they will continue to ripen after they reach room temperature.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which word refers to the study of bones?", "correct_answer": "osteology", "incorrect_answers": ["otology", "endocrinology", "neropathp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The subject that studies the solution of a system of linear inequalities is called Linear Programming. Which of these men was most instrumental in its development?", "correct_answer": "George B. Dantzig", "incorrect_answers": ["Sir Isaac Barrow", "Sir Isaac Newton", "Alfred Whitehead"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "2007 marked what approximate number of people living on our planet?", "correct_answer": "6,600,000,000", "incorrect_answers": ["60,000,000,000", "660,000,000,000", "6,600,000,000,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 1000 people, how many would be doctors?", "correct_answer": "1", "incorrect_answers": ["16", "29", "5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of traditional ritual is the Famadihana, practiced by the Malagasy people in Madagascar?", "correct_answer": "Turning of the dead", "incorrect_answers": ["Circumcision", "Introducing boys into manhood by tattooing and scarring them", "Animal sacrifice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of color is the color named thistle?", "correct_answer": "Purple", "incorrect_answers": ["Green", "Brown", "Yellow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It takes 40 litres (10 gallons) of maple sap to make 2 litres (a half gallon) of maple syrup.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how long is a Red Foxs gestation period?", "correct_answer": "55 days", "incorrect_answers": ["89 days", "40 days", "34 days"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which U.S. president had the first bowling alley put in the White House?", "correct_answer": "Truman", "incorrect_answers": ["Nixon", "Eisenhower", "Taft"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If at noon on the 2nd of February you see this animals shadow, be sure the weather will be cold.", "correct_answer": "A groundhog", "incorrect_answers": ["A weasel", "A hedgehog", "A hog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This scientist, winner of the 1908 Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine, was the first to notice the existence of blood-brain barrier.", "correct_answer": "Paul Ehrlich", "incorrect_answers": ["Edwin Goldman", "Dr. Marian Diamond", "Walter Dandy"]}]